Ming-Ju Kuo

Tel: (571)320-7901 | Email: kuo.ming.ju@gmail.com | Personal Website: https://ntueeboy.github.io

Summary

Incoming CS master's student at Virginia Tech. Software engineer intern at Taiwan AI Labs and two years of experience in software industry. Proven ability to develop and test web-based applications. Experienced the agile (Scrum) and CI/CD pipeline with GitHub Actions and Gitlab pipeline.

Education

Virginia Tech, Falls Church, VA	08/2023 - 12/2024
MEng in Computer Science	
Technical University of Dresden, Dresden, Germany	10/2016 - 09/2019
MSc in Bioengineering	
National Taiwan University, Taipei, Taiwan	09/2010 - 06/2015
BSc in Life Science and Geosciences (double major)	

Non-degree Certificate

Fu Jen Catholic University, New Taipei City, Taiwan

09/2021 - 06/2022

Software Engineering program

Relevant Course: Linear Algebra, Discrete Math, Data Structures, Algorithms, and Operating System

Professional Experience

Taiwan AI Labs, Taipei, Taiwan

06/2023 – present

Software Engineer Intern

- Developing APIs for the bioinformatics platform (<u>GenDiseak</u>) to execute the bio-analysis pipeline.
- Modularizing the task management functionality into a microservice architecture to ensure scalability and mitigate race conditions and deploying the service to Kubernetes clusters.

Lyntics GmbH, Munich, Germany

04/2022 - 01/2023

Junior Software Engineer

- Designed Restful APIs for the web application to handle complicated user permission logic.
- Cooperated with front-end engineers to integrate React with well-defined APIs.
- Developed unit tests for APIs and integrated the tests with Bitbucket pipeline for CI/CD.
- Created the microservice such as NGINX for web encryption and reverse proxy.

NZXT, Inc., Taipei, Taiwan

12/2020 - 03/2022

Junior Software QA Engineer

- Implemented end-to-end test automation for the e-commerce website and the web-based desktop application (CAM) with CucumberJS in TypeScript to ensure the quality of applications.
- Integrated GitHub Action CI workflow with TestRail and Slack API to report the daily test result.
- Designed the test cases to cover all the new features as much as possible.

Skills

Programming	TypeScript, Python
Framework	NestJS, express,
Tools	Git, Docker, Kubernetes, Slack API, TestRail API

Publications

A Acevedo, Sara Ciucci, **MJ Kuo**, Claudio Durán, Carlo V Cannistraci. Measuring group-separability in geometrical space for evaluation of pattern recognition and embedding algorithms (**IEEE Access**)